{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-10",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 10",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "english-5",
    "unit10",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 10: Our school trip",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "trip",
      "answer": "chuyến đi",
      "speak": "trip"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "hill",
      "answer": "đồi",
      "speak": "hill"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "lake",
      "answer": "hồ",
      "speak": "lake"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "theme park",
      "answer": "công viên giải trí",
      "speak": "theme park"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "market",
      "answer": "chợ",
      "speak": "market"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "eco-tour",
      "answer": "du lịch sinh thái",
      "speak": "eco-tour"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "arrive",
      "answer": "đến nơi",
      "speak": "arrive"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "vegetable",
      "answer": "rau củ",
      "speak": "vegetable"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "beautiful",
      "answer": "xinh đẹp",
      "speak": "beautiful"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "great",
      "answer": "tuyệt vời",
      "speak": "great"
    }
  ]
}